Huh?
I choose to not understand these signs.
- A-ha.
- B... Bender.
I was just not playing the Holophonor.
Yeah? Well, you should try
not stinking at it.
Well, I am trying.
I've been taking lessons.
Lessons? Ha, that's rich.
Isn't it time you gave up all hope
of ever improving yourself in any way?
I know I should, but I just can't.
Remember when I had
those stomach worms that made me smart?
I could play the Holophonor,
and it made Leela like me.
Hey, Bender, as long as you know,
I have a Holophonor recital Tuesday
and I'd really like
to have somebody there. Please?
Fine, I'll go already.
You know, sometimes I wish
your real parents were still alive.
Not often, though.
Whoa, whoa. Whoa, whoa.
Hey.
- Uh, hello, Mrs. Mellinger.
- Hello, Philip.
And you must be Mr. Bender.
Philip's told me so much about you.
Is it true that you're a robot?
I prefer the term "Love machine."
Wow, your kid is great.
How hard did you say you had to hit him?
Fairly hard.
The Grumpy Snail.
Sorry.
It's too grumpy.
Whoo!
Mr. Bender, I simply
cannot teach your child.
Then good day, madam.
We hope to see you soon for tea.
It's hopeless.
I can hear all this great music in my head
but my stupid hands can't keep up.
Aw, you know what always cheers me up?
Laughing at other
people's misfortunes.
Hey, guys, you missed
a great delivery to Space Earth.
Where you been all afternoon?
At a... A concert.
Ooh, was it jazz noodling?
My ex-boyfriend Sean played the sax.
I used to listen for hours
while he sat naked on my couch
and improvised.
So, musicians really
Rodger your Hammerstein, huh?
Yeah, it's weird.
Sean was uneducated, unambitious,
- he was pasty and hunched...
- Pretty boy.
...but when he played
I could sense this incredible,
beautiful, creative soul.
Then one day, I found someone else's
couch fibers on his butt.
I couldn't even believe that.
It was really...
That could be my beautiful soul
sitting naked on her couch
if I could just
learn to play this stupid thing.
Oh, but you can.
Though you may have to metaphorically
"make a deal with the Devil."
And by "Devil," I mean Robot Devil,
and by "Metaphorically,"
I mean get your coat.
You hit a sour note
about 200 years back, Doug.
Let's take it from the top.
Ah, Bender, Fry!
You've come back
for more eternal damnation.
No, this isn't a religious visit.
Fry just wants Holophonor lessons.
Yep. I need to get
really good without practicing.
Hell is full of ten-year-olds
who wanted exactly the same thing.
Trouble is, you have
what my old music teacher
Mrs. Mellinger, calls "Stupid Fingers."
With hands like that
you'll be lucky to master a belt buckle.
Now, wouldn't it be nice
if you had a pair of robot hands
to replace them?
Sure would.
Oh, well. Good-bye.
Fry, you smelly idiot.
I think he's willing to make some kind
of a deal with the Devil with you.
He... He is? Great.
Wait, what's the catch?
No catch.
I'll merely pick a robot at random
from somewhere in the universe,
probably one you've never even met,
and then I'll remove his hands
and switch them for yours.
It's just the sort of guy I am.
What do you say?
Uh, I don't know.
It doesn't seem entirely moral to...
Fry, if you don't take
this offer right now
I will lose all respect
for you and punch you.
Well... all right.
You're sure I probably won't know him?
Definitely probably not.
- Just sign this contract...
- Wow.
And here we go.
I got a hundred bucks on Rectal-Exam-Bot.
"Robot Devil?"
I get your hands? 'Zam!
Oh, what an appallingly ironic outcome.
It's not ironic. It's just coincidental.
Now fork over those ladyfingers, cookie.
You know, I only put my name on there
as a show of good faith
for the other robots.
Stop being such a baby
and chop my hands off.
Oh, very well.
How'd you do that?
They're very good hands.
At last.
At last I have the power
to make Leela love me.
Oh, sorry.
That'll wear off in a couple of days.
Check it out, everyone. I'm back from Hell
and I've got the Robot Devil's hands.
Neat. Let's see a trick.
All righty.
Somebody called the Robot Devil's here
to see somebody called Fry.
Uh-oh.
Where'd I go just now?
Hello, Fry.
Just dropped by to make sure
you're as happy
with our little deal as I am.
Oh... give me back my hands.
These things are always
touching me in places.
Yeah, they get around,
but I'm afraid we had a deal.
Looks like I wasted a bus trip.
Yes, you did.
Yes, now you can hear
Holophonor virtuoso Philip Fry
play 900 of these classic themes
in your own home
on this two-record set.
That's over 30 minutes
of music for only $14.99.
Only $14.99 for a two-record set.
Two records.
Oh, Zoidberg, at last you're
becoming a crafty consumer.
- Hello.
- Hello? I'll take eight.
A Mr. Hedonismbot to see you.
- Uh, show him in.
- Very good, sir.
Ah, Fry, congratulations.
Your latest performance was as delectable
as dipping my bottom over and over
into a bath
of the silkiest oils and creams.
Thank you, sir.
That's exactly what I was going for.
You were the sole diversion
in what has been a pale
and un-amusing season,
and so, I would fain commission
you write an opera.
But I've never written an opera.
And I've never heard one.
Still, if you can keep me amused
through the overture
I shall consider it a smashing success.
But I wouldn't even know
what to write about. Unless...
Okay, I'll do it
if I can make it about Leela.
Me? Really?
A man writing an opera about a woman?
Oh, sirrah, how deliciously absurd.
I shall see you at the premiere.
Is it part of the opera?
Leela. You shouldn't be listening.
I don't want you to hear it
till it's done.
But it's so beautiful.
So is a peacock,
but you don't eat it until it's cooked.
This has to be perfect.
I want you to hear exactly what I hear
when I think about you.
Oh, Fry, all this time
you've had this incredible gift
and I never knew.
I've been a fool,
a fully justified, prudent fool.
They're so cold.
And yet Hell is so hot.
Can I have my hands back now?
- No!
- You're not nice.
Ah, Bender, this is a surprise...
for you, finding me in the refrigerator.
True, but at least
I don't have the hiccups anymore.
- What up?
- Oh, well, it so happens
I'm in the mood to make a deal with you.
- Forget it. you can't tempt me.
- Really?
There's nothing you want?
Hmm. I forgot you could tempt me
with things I want.
Well, I suppose I've always wondered
what it would be like
to be more annoying.
Nothing simpler,
and all I ask in return is your hands
to replace these bony hot dogs.
Grabby and Squeezy?
Never. I love these guys.
Well, is there anything else
you would part with?
No, nothing, ain't gonna happen.
Yes. With this built-in stadium air horn
I can really annoy people
and all it cost me was my crotch plate.
You certainly are
a shrewd businessman, Bender.
Now find someone
and give them a good blast.
Yeah, that'll teach
the first person I see a lesson.
Ah, my ridiculously circuitous plan
is one quarter complete.
Well, Fry's opera
premieres tomorrow night.
I'm off to find a pair of formal gloves
that will fit over my enormous forearms.
Pretty annoying, huh, Leela?
What? Are you talking?
Oh, God, I'm deaf.
Oops. I'm so, so sorry, Leela.
I just wanted to annoy you.
What? Oh, this is horrible.
I won't be able to hear Fry's opera.
Ah, how delightfully ironic.
It's not ironic.
It's just mean. Take this.
Ooh, out of aerosol.
Also ironic.
Oh, yeah?
Well, bite my shiny metal...
Oh, no!
Nobody tell Fry I'm deaf.
If he found out I couldn't hear his opera,
it'd break his heart.
Okay, deaf-o.
Courtesans and gentlefops,
I bid you welcome to my opera.
Let us cavort like the Greeks of old.
You know the ones I mean.
Yay, Fry.
I watch TV with that guy.
Who is this one-eyed
female baby Moses?
With courage in her female baby smile?
A savior from the stars
Or something stranger still?
Or just a lonely, filthy, starving child?
Amy, Fry's looking at me.
What am I supposed to be feeling?
Ah.
Leela
Leela, Leela
Save him
Save Fry, save Fry
Godzilla will devour him
As for me, I must be off
To have my doctor check this cough
Good-bye
I don't recall ever fighting Godzilla,
but that is so what I would have done.
Oh, it was a lovely show.
One diet double martini, please.
And for you, sir?
I'll just have a Shirley Hemphill.
Extra, extra.
World's greatest opera only half over.
Half over? Oh!
I'd give anything to hear the rest.
Anything?
Thank you, sir.
Now, as I was saying...
Anything?
Because I can give you new robotic ears.
What? You can give me new ears?
Wait. What seemingly reasonable thing
do you want in return?
Just your hands, my dear.
Whatever you said, forget it.
All right, then. Just one hand.
Just... my left hand?
Um...
Please take your seats for act two.
But I'm not done vomiting.
I can't stand it.
Okay, you can have my hand.
Wonderful! Just sign here.
Calculon, old friend,
I'm afraid I need your ears.
Well, I do owe you
for giving me this unholy...
acting talent.
I can hear. I can hear like a safecracker.
Hey, aren't you gonna take my hand?
In good time. You go enjoy the opera.
To win Leela's heart
with the Holophonor's art
I need hands of transcendental quickness
Well, I don't see any danger
In gambling with a stranger
For my head is ofa most amazing thickness
I'm stupid, I'm stupid
I'm stupider than you
I'm stupider than you in every way
Stupider?
This opera is as lousy
as it is brilliant.
Your lyrics lack subtlety.
You can't just have your characters
announce how they feel.
That makes me feel angry.
Look, what do you want?
I want my hands back
Never.
A deal's a deal
Even with a dirty dealer
Very well, then I'll take
What I want from Leela
Whoa.
Leela has promised me her hand
Fry, you do not understand!
I should have revealed
I'd been deafened by Bender
The shame
The shame!
But I feared you'd stop writing
This musical splendor
Deception's the curse
of my whimsical gender
He gave me mechanical ears
Effective, though just a bit garish
In return, without shedding a tear
I agreed that I'd give him my hand
In marriage
- Huh?
- What?
You'll give me your hand in marriage
Is this really happening
Or just being staged?
It can't be real
Not if Leela is engaged
That isn't what I meant
That isn't what I signed
You should have checked the wording
In the fine...
Print
"I'll give you my hand..."
In marriage
The use of words
expressing something other
Than their literal intention
Now that is irony
I will marry her now
and confine her to Hell
How droll
Where Styx is a river
And not just a band
Though they'll play our reception
If all goes as planned
Unless Fry, you surrender my hands!
Destiny has cheated me
By forcing me to decide upon
The woman that I idolize
Or the hands of an automaton
Without these hands I can't complete
The opera that was captivating her
But if keep them, and she marries him
Then he probably won't want me dating her
Arooo.
Brave-o.
En-core.
I can't believe
the devil is so unforgiving
everybody's just ad-libbing
By the power vested in me
By the state of New New York...
No! Stop.
Take my hands...
You evil... metal... dork!
Surgery in an opera?
How wonderfully decadent.
And just as I was beginning
to lose interest.
Jambi, the chocolate icing.
Oh, my, yes.
Ooh.
My hands.
My horrible human hands.
And what did you do to my nails?
I cleaned them.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
it's my poker night
and I feel lucky.
So, it's back to Hell for me.
- Come on, Nixon.
- Huh?
Less reality, more fantasy.
Resume the opera.
But I can't play anymore.
Yes, you can.
The beauty was in your heart,
not your hands.
Your music's bad, and you should feel bad.
Whoa.
Hey.
Extra, extra.
Greatest opera of all time sucks.
I'll take eight.
Please don't stop playing, Fry.
I want to hear how it ends.